Let's pray, Father God, we love you, God, we're so grateful for this community that you
place us in. God, I'm thankful for the leadership that we have and I just pray for your peace
and your prosperity for all of us. God, you place these people in their position to lead us well
and God, I just pray that you remind them of that but also give them the courage and confidence
that they need to make good decisions and that'd be for the betterment of all of us. God,
we just pray that mine was a great place to grow up, raise a family and to retire in all those
things and Father, you can do that for us. We love you, we pray that we become more like Jesus
every day. It's in His name we pray. Amen. Amen. I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States
of America and to the Republic for which it spans one nation under God in the visible
with liberty and justice for all of us. For a public embedment, it's good that personal appearances
five points list. Most to a proof. Second, he stepped like Barnes. I've Joins, I don't know.
Six minutes from the March 25th, 2025, regular meeting.
Much to proof. Second, he stepped like Barnes, I've Joins, I don't know. Hi. Parker.
I'm seven, budget, budget, budget, amendment 25-20.
So, you'll see three minutes tonight. This is the first one. This essentially, it moves money
to cover an under-budgeted OWRB loan payment. The information came in light. It was not budgeted.
So, second. Thanks. Thank you, Jen. All right. Barnes, I'm Darryle Cole. Hi. Parker.
Hey, the discussion about the possible action regarding amendment.
C-23-0-8C with B-3 construction.
And C-Z-23-0-8C with Stel and Brown Reynolds.
So, these are the tipping and transport fees for some of the ways the original contracts were lit in between
the city of Miami and the companies. So, it's actually between MSUA and the companies.
So, we are drafted in amendment and I believe the companies have agreed to it.
the companies of R&D agree to it. It's just changing the name to MSU on the contract or the parties.
Hi, Parker.
Hi.
Now in contract amendments with Republic Services, also known as BFI,
Voice Services, C-23-080,
Services C-23-280 and B-3 construction C-23-080.
This will be the last year that we renew on the contract that was made a couple of years ago.
This will go through April 30th, the 2026.
Stella, environmental who halls all of the solid waste,
they deliberate to BFI and what we call Republic Services.
They were trying to increase it by 5.2%.
They ended up settling with a 3% increase.
We want to continue with the M-right now.
Back when they won the bid, they won, and they said it's about 95 cents less per ton.
We just to give you an idea of this year, we're at 12,615 tons,
5 March from July 1 through March 1.
We hall a lot of solid waste, but the 3% increase will only increase by 79 cents.
We're getting back up to where we close to about where we broke in before we got the contract.
B-3 construction, that's where we take our demolition material and the price will stay the same with them.
We actually haven't used them this year because we're not as heavy into knocking down homes
and things like that.
So if you want to, they know with them.
BFI services, they ask for a 4.44% increase.
They settle for a 3% as well.
It's actually a 69-cent cost increase per ton.
Back when we, before we got the contract going, they were at 451 per ton.
And they ended up dropping that to 25-20 when we got the contract going a couple of years ago.
So it's the 69-cent increase.
It still makes it a great savings compared to what we've won.
So we recommend renewing all of these contracts as the current market cost has increased,
but it's still better to take this and go back out to bed again.
and we will have to at the end of this one here.
25?
Tell them we're in budget for this every year.
1.1 million.
I know it's right there.
It says 1.1 million.
I don't check with Terry.
What is 1.1 million?
So this looks like it's going to take us up to 1.3.
So we're going to have to do budget amendments to take care of the overageer.
Hopefully we will be able to stay in that 1.1.
I'm going to make it next year.
We're working on next year's budget right now.
So we budgeted more money in our tipping fees to kind of for this.
So you said it was we're at 12,000.
12,615 tons right now.
So we take 50,000 a year.
Is that pretty good?
We take what?
22 tons, 22,000 tons.
Things are high.
That are lower.
Yeah.
Really.
So is the reason that we took more in the...
Because if you do the math in your extrapolate,
we're in the first quarter and we've taken 12,000 tons already.
That's 50,000 tons for the year.
You're saying the first quarter.
That's what he said.
You said so far this year up to March.
We've hauled 12,600 tons.
It's cool.
No, that's July.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
My bet.
So you're saying the...
I understand your saying now.
That's my math, not math, because I'm in different fiscal quarters in my...
Right.
I'm going to make some.
Thank you.
What's your number?
Second.
Joe's five.
E7.
Aaron Ryan.
Barnes.
Hi.
Joe's five.
Parker.
She's having a problem.
Yeah.
I'm going to do this.
If any of which is...
What's your goodness?
Supposing this again?
No, I'm testing.
You know what?
Well done.
Motion.
Second.
Who's seconded?
Hi.
Yeah.
I'll do it.
Joe's five.
Hi.
E7.
Parker.